[
  {
    "question": "The tectonic plates form?",
    "optionOne": "The listhophere.",
    "optionTwo": "The asthenosphere.",
    "optionThree": "The paleosphere.",
    "correctAnswer": "The listhophere."
  },
  {
    "question": "Except tectonic plates boundaries, where can we find volcanoes?",
    "optionOne": "In hotzones.",
    "optionTwo": "In hotspots.",
    "optionThree": "At subduction zones.",
    "correctAnswer": "In hotspots."
  },
  {
    "question": "At what rate tectonic plates progress?",
    "optionOne": "Between 3 and 5cms a year.",
    "optionTwo": "Between 5 and 8cms a year.",
    "optionThree": "Between 8 and 10cms a year.",
    "correctAnswer": "Between 3 and 5cms a year."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a tectonic boundary type?",
    "optionOne": "Divergent.",
    "optionTwo": "Transform.",
    "optionThree": "Adjacent.",
    "correctAnswer": "Adjacent."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a tectonic boundary type?",
    "optionOne": "Opposite.",
    "optionTwo": "Convergent.",
    "optionThree": "Lateral.",
    "correctAnswer": "Convergent."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which volcano type creates hudge crater?",
    "optionOne": "Composite volcano.",
    "optionTwo": "Dome volcano.",
    "optionThree": "Caldera volcano.",
    "correctAnswer": "Caldera volcano."
  },
  {
    "question": "What characterize volcano types?",
    "optionOne": "The lava flow.",
    "optionTwo": "The slope angle or steepness.",
    "optionThree": "The explosion's violence.",
    "correctAnswer": "The lava flow."
  },
  {
    "question": "What characterized volcanic eruption in detailed classification?",
    "optionOne": "Seismologic activity and ground composition.",
    "optionTwo": "Volcanic activity type and location.",
    "optionThree": "Tectonic plates names that created them.",
    "correctAnswer": "Volcanic activity type and location."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a type erruption?",
    "optionOne": "Hawaiian.",
    "optionTwo": "Pelean.",
    "optionThree": "Italian.",
    "correctAnswer": "Italian."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the most destructive and intense volcanic erruption?",
    "optionOne": "Plinian.",
    "optionTwo": "Icelandic.",
    "optionThree": "Stombolian.",
    "correctAnswer": "Plinian."
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of glass lava can create?",
    "optionOne": "Vesicles.",
    "optionTwo": "Obsidian.",
    "optionThree": "Basalt.",
    "correctAnswer": "Obsidian."
  },
  {
    "question": "What can create volcanic chain?",
    "optionOne": "Earthquakes.",
    "optionTwo": "Magma chambers.",
    "optionThree": "Hotspots.",
    "correctAnswer": "Hotspots."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hottest lava temperature?",
    "optionOne": "About 1100 celsius degree.",
    "optionTwo": "About 800 celsius degree.",
    "optionThree": "About 100 celsius degree.",
    "correctAnswer": "About 1100 celsius degree."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a plume composed of?",
    "optionOne": "Volcanic water.",
    "optionTwo": "Volcanic ash.",
    "optionThree": "Volcanic smoke.",
    "correctAnswer": "Volcanic ash."
  }
]